(Raj:)Since you two are gonna be
around for Valentine's,
(Raj:)would you mind
watching Cinnamon?
(Penny:)You have Valentine's plans?
(Penny:)Which came out sounding way
more surprised than I meant.
(Penny:)Let me try that again.
You have Val--
(Penny:)-See? I can't do it.
-I don't have plans,
(Raj:)which is why I booked time
on the big telescope that night.
(Amy:)Well, an evening looking at the
stars, that's still kind of romantic.
(Raj:)Except I'll be alone.
(Amy:)I'm trying to put lipstick
on a pig here. Work with me.
(Leonard:)-We'd be happy to watch Cinnamon.
-Yeah.
(Raj:)Thank you. Oh, and I'd like
for at least one of us
(Raj:)to see some action, so if you
guys happen to have sex,
(Raj:)it's cool if she stays in the room.
(Penny:)Same goes for the
two of you with Amy.
(Amy:)What do you think, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)It's magnificent.
(Sheldon:)This is going to be
the best Valentine's Day ever.